Look Lappu, son Paplu, tomorrow we will go on a picnic, bring
₹100, okay, okay,
what happened friend,
my mother will not give me ₹100,
friend, this is your usual drama, you bring 90, 90,
yes 90, now if you are not able to bring even this much then all
three of us will go, now if you are not
able to bring even this much then all three of us will go, don't follow
me, don't drive me crazy,
hey mom, give it to me, it is just a matter of ₹100,
in our times, two pairs of clothes could be bought for ₹100.  They must be
coming mom, now only
40 chocolates come.  You want to eat 40 chocolates.
Come, I will get it from the shop next door.
Oh no, mom, please give me the money.  Look,
I will not give you the money.  Go and ask your father.
Dad to mom,
dad will not give.
You know that.
Why is this calculator not working?
Yes,
what happened?
Nothing, dad.
Tell me quickly, don't bother me.
Papa, I needed those ₹100.
No, no, it is not necessary like that.  Don't give meaning.
Not 100.  If you want 50 then tell me.   Are
?  If you want 50 then tell me.   If it's
not done, let it be.
Yes, now you will not be able to bring even this much, all three of us will leave.
Okay listen,
yes dad.  I have a torn ₹100 note.  If you want to
drive, drive it.
[Music]
Yes, Chhotu, tell me
brother, give me a 10 rupee Dairy Milk.
Chhotu, give me a dairy milk.
[MUSIC]
What more do you want?
What else do you want, little one?
[music]